(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
Zein,
what's this?
What happened to you?
It’s Supremo.
Don't make any more offenses.
Next time, you won't be as lucky.
There’s this girl…
I heard from some students
that she's stubborn and rebellious.
Keep an eye on her.
Zein, it's 7:00 p.m.
One!
Two!
Three!
This isn't an ordinary nail.
There's poison and tetanus in it.
Let's be grateful that
someone saved you.
You hear that, Zein?
Lesson learned.
It's better to hold your pee in
instead of risking your life.
Sorry, Van.
Look who's apologizing.
Sorry guys.
We're going to be late.
Let’s go?
Are you sure you're not
going to class?
I want to stay by Matt's side.
It's my fault this
happened to him.
Okay, we'll head out.
Zein...
you take care of Matt, okay?
Keep your eyes on him!
On Matt!
Alright, I hear you.
Matt...
are you awake?
How are you feeling?
Are you hurt?
Are you okay?
Hey...
Are you hungry?
Thirsty?
Matt...
Have you gone insane?
Or has the poison reached your brain?
Pepper.
This will purge-
the rest of the poison from my body.
It's so spicy!
It's too hot!
You find that funny?
Hey!
Why did you block it?
If I only knew you we're joking,
I would've punched you harder.
You thought the BBG’s nail was lethal?
Wait until you taste this.
Let me see this...
This?
That's nothing!
So you're challenging me?
You bet!
- Come on.
- Game?
Let's do it!
- Get ready!
- Try me.
Game.
Give me your best shot.
- Can you handle it?
- Of course!
How dare you!
You know...
Zein...
Zein.
Thank you.
Zein...
I wanted to thank you.
Cause even if it was dangerous out there
you still didn't leave me.
Sorry if you almost got hurt because of me.
Sorry...
Sorry?
It was my fault.
What happened to you was my fault.
I just did the right thing.
It was nothing.
You know...
before I fainted.
I saw the guy with the mask.
His mask was red while
the ones chasing us
their masks were black.
What if...
their gangs have
designated mask colors?
Right?
If the ones chasing us
were the Black Blood Gang...
I'm certain that the one
who helped us
was part of the
Devil God Warrior.
I saw fear in their eyes...
and their knees were shaking.
They all left in an instant.
That guy must not be
an ordinary member.
I think...
he must be Raze Silvenia.
The leader of the
Devil God Warrior.
But why would he help us?
I don't know either, Zein.
I ask myself that question too.
When we were running
away from them...
I already noticed
something watching us.
If he's from the
Black Blood Gang,
he would've killed us already.
Is it possible that
Raze was there?
Was the Devil God Warrior
out there that night?
It's possible.
But why?
We won't find answers
to our questions.
For now,
what we can do is rest.
And try to catch up
on our classes.
Let's show everyone
in Hell University
that they don't scare us.
We're going to be late!
What time is it?
I want to go to class.
Let's go?
We're already late.
Come on!
Just a minute, it still hurts.
Can you handle yourself?
My lips are still pale, Zein.
Miss...
are you okay?
Are you alright?
What happened?
No, please!
Good morning class.
Before anything else...
I have a big announcement!
Well, it's been a while
since we've had this event
or any event for that matter.
That is why
I am so happy to announce
on behalf of the
Hell U administration
that we will be having another
acquaintance party!
I know. I'm sure you're all excited.
That's why we hope
that you keep that enthusiasm
as we roll out details
in the incoming days.
Teacher Kath?
Yes, Celine?
I think...
this isn't the right time to celebrate.
Especially from the deaths
these past few weeks...
It is unfortunately out
of my hands, Celine.
Madam Violet has
made her decision.
And things are already moving
to have it done by this Friday.
But...
don't you also have
the power to stop the event?
Maybe you could reason
with Madam Violet-
Enough, Celine!
Like I said...
more details will be rolled
over the coming days.
Now, we still have class.
Let's start!
So last time if you remember,
we talked about energy, right?
Potential and kinetic energy.
Acquaintance party?
What are they planning to do?
Whatever they're planning on
and whoever started this...
my friends and I aren't pushovers.
We're not afraid of you...
The admin,
the Black Blood Gang,
or the Devil God Warrior.
They should be the
ones afraid of us.
Excuse me, sir?
Boss...
Is this your only branch?
Or are there others?
Don't be rude!
Thank you!
Thank you.
Matt...
you sure you're okay?
Don't you need to rest more?
I'm okay.
The pepper took care
of the poison.
Eat another one so you're sure.
Purge it out of you.
What?
You know what...
while you're busy with
your inside jokes
Dave and Jerome have
been looking for ways
to escape this place.
Because of what happened
with you both last night...
my God!
We need to act faster.
We tried to find the road
that led us here...
but it's so strange
it seems like the roads
have changed.
Any road we walk on...
it leads us to nowhere.
What are we going to do?
We entered this
place unknowingly...
We don't know it's history
or who runs this place.
We need information
so we can fight back
and escape.
If we need to kill
to escape, so be it!
We need to strike first
to get leverage.
From the tone of that voice of yours...
I'm sure you have a plan.
Celine.
She knows something.
I thought of the same thing...
but she's wary of us.
It's like she's afraid of us.
I'll handle that.
Maybe she has information
about the gangs here too...
We need to find a way
to deal with those gangs.
No!
I don't think it's the right decision
to meddle with the gangs.
Why are you overreacting?
It's not like that.
But after what happened
last night...
maybe it's better to investigate
about the University itself?
If the gangs find out that
we're asking too many
questions about them...
we can get hurt.
Dave.
If we know the
history of this place
everything will align.
The substantial part
of HU's history
are the gangs.
It doesn't matter which
one we prod first.
We need information to fight this battle.
That's why we need
to find answers.
You're right.
Let's try to find information
our own way.
Now's the time.
Let's realign later.
Celine!
Come on, let's go.
Hold on.
I won't hurt you.
I just want to talk.
Stay away from us.
We don't want you to get hurt.
It's too late for that.
We've been marked since
we entered this place.
Please...
we need your help.
Celine...
It's okay.
Not here.
I need to ask you this, Zein.
Are you ready...
to trade your life-
for this information?
Tell me everything you know.
You're brave now, Zein.
You are brave.
You are brave...
But...
they used to be brave like you.
The previous newbies.
They were more curious than brave.
Remember.
It's easy to ask questions.
But it's difficult to handle
the burden of the truth.
Try me.
Hell University was once called-
“Philippine High University.”
Only the children of the wealthy
and powerful can enter this school.
But...
everything changed.
When the founder, Dr. Quizon,
lost his mind.
He was a well known scientist.
But he used this school's
high tuition fees
to fund his research.
He slowly lost his mind
and used the students within
the university in his obsession.
A formula-
who can revive the dead.
Immortality
and revival.
One day.
Everybody was blindsided.
All the exits have been blocked.
There was no way out.
The admins managed to find a way
to hide the whole university
from the whole country.
Nobody had the power to do
anything, even the parents.
I was one of the first students
who got trapped in this hellhole.
We don't know how
but it's like we've been sealed
inside a hidden pocket universe.
They used all of us
in his experiments.
The ones who died first
were the lucky ones.
It was chaos.
Some tried to fight back,
some rebelled.
But most turned on each other to release
their rage. It didn't take long before.
PHU turned into Hell U.
From the chaos and bloodshed
many gangs were formed.
You already know the two
most powerful gangs here.
The Black Blood Gang
and The Devil God Warrior.
Dr. Quizon completed the formula
but he died before he
could use it for himself.
There were rumors saying that
a student got his hands
on the formula.
That student is still in Hell U.
That's why they locked this
place from the world.
The officals and the forces outside
are still looking for that student
because they're desperate to
get a hold of that formula.
Zein,
that's Hell U's secret.
That's why no one is allowed to leave.
They believe that student
is still here.
It could be anyone.
That person's life is in danger.
I’m sure
it'll only take a while
before the officials find
out who that student is.
You know what I'm more afraid of?
The formula getting-
into the hands of the wrong people.
And using it for evil.
Now you know the secret of Hell U.
You will never get to leave.
You will die here.
Do you know the student
who has the formula?
If you do know...
it's time to take extra precautions.
Because it's hard to get
out of this-
once you've become involved.
You'll get involved, Zein.
You'll get involved.
I talk big about how
information is our weapon.
What am I supposed
to do with Celine’s story?
Should I tell the others what I found out?
They might just get dragged into this.
But if I keep quiet...
Did you like Celine's story?
You don't know how
to listen, do you?
I know everything.
Everything?
Don't be so sure.
That's only half of the story.
You don't know everything yet, Zein.
But you went ahead and
made yourself a target anyway.
Brace yourself.
You're going to die soon.
What happened?
Are you okay?
It's Ms. Leonora, the librarian.
She tried to scare us off.
What did she say?
She said that the cost of the
information we're looking for
is being stuck here
in HU permanently.
That's what the students
we asked said too.
It was creepy.
She kept on saying:
There's a cost
in the information
you're looking for.
Leave this place!
She didn't answer our question
but she said something about
being able to leave this place.
Vanessa and I waited for
all of us to be complete
before we shared this information.
What is it? She showed
you the way out?
We need to get up
the ranks in HU.
Rank?
What rank?
You mean the classroom rankings?
Top achievers?
Not just in the classroom...
The overall HU rankings.
This is the list.
As of now, Raze Silvenia is
in the top of the ranks.
Give me that.
Not that, the cookies!
Jerome, you're so annoying.
Nazzer Lumia.
I think he's the leader of
the Black Blood Gang.
Both the leaders
of the two most powerful gangs
are in the top of the ranks.
I don't think that's a coincidence.
It could be a lead.
I think you're right!
But it's clear to me
that if we ask more
information about Hell University,
we'll be in more danger
that we already are.
Information about this school,
the gangs...
But this...
I'm sure if we try to get into the ranks
we won't be hurt.
We just need to be good students.
We need to work hard to
get into the top ten rank.
We'll make it out alive.
How about you, Zein?
Did you find any answers?
What did Celine tell you?
I cannot tell them what I found out.
Give me that! Hey!
That's his third warning.
Really?
That's the last warning.
They might bring him to
the Dark Hell Jail.
As you can see
the festival committee is
working so hard
to finish the decorations
for this Friday's event.
Despite the very tight schedule,
they're doing everything they can
to make it as smooth as possible.
I'm sure you've guessed from the decor
but I'm going to make it official.
That this Friday's event
is going to be a masquerade.
Masks are mandatory.
While we encourage creativity
and freedom of expression,
we highly prohibit the use of two colors.
Red and black.
These colors are exclusive
for the Devil God Warrior and
the Black Blood Gang.
Non members cannot
use these colors.
To ensure compliance, we're gonna
send your outfits to your dorm.
Feel free to make your masks.
We'll call next Friday,
Free Bloody Night.
Where killing is prohibited.
Breaking this rule
is punishable by death.
Now, I'd like to call on
Supreme Student President.
Ace Craige for more announcements.
Thank you, Madam Violet.
Some pressing concerns will
prevent me from attending
this Friday's festivities.
In short, I won't be there.
Why is he not attending?
But beware...
I will be watching you.
Wanted: Supreme Student
Government Secretary.
Aren’t you going to
step out of my way?
Should I?
I'm the Supreme Student
Government Secretary here.
Miss... I don't care who you are.
Former secretary.
Can't you read?
Or should I read it for you?
That's just a paper.
A mistake, obviously!
I haven't stepped down
from my position!
Stop complaining.
You've been kicked
out of your position.
Miss...
Fritzy.
I don't care about your name.
Maybe you're just not qualified.
What are you doing?
How dare you!
Stop them!
What the fuck is wrong with you?
You don’t have the right to hurt
the Supreme Student Secretary!
An insult to one of us
is an insult to all of us!
Do I look like I care?
Mark my words...
I will use eveything in
my power to crush you.
You won't be able to
escape my grudge.
You can use all the power you have
but it doesn't change the fact
that Fritzy is a bitch
and you are an asshole.
If you hit her...
that would've been a third
warning for you
and the former secretary
Mr. President, my
sincerest apologies.
I want this room cleared!
On my command!
One.
President, if you would
let me explain
it isn't Fritzy's fault.
It was this good for nothing.
It's this bitch who started-
Two.
Kill me now.
Not yet, Ms. Shion.
You need to heal before
you face your punishment, okay?
Cause you're the type of bitch
that’s qualified to be my secretary.
So you need to be
treated immediately.
Kill me now.
Nurse Cha!
Supremo...
I don't want to see any
scars on her forehead.
Let me check on her.
I can't guarantee you
that it won't leave a scar.
Well, you wouldn't let that
happen to my secretary.
Right, Nurse Cha?
Patch her up.
Now.
Yes, Supremo.
Hey, I didn't agree
to that position yet.
What happened to Zein?
What happened to her?
Oh my God, Zein!
What did you get
yourself into this time
that the SSG President
did that to you?
President?
The whole school's been
talking about it.
Others said that the
President did this to you.
A lot of people saw it, Zein.
They're just making up stories.
Who would you believe?
Me?
Or other people?
Onel was the one who pushed me
because I got into a fight with
his bitch of a girlfriend.
I knew it! You started
something again.
Am I just going to let the queen
bee wannabees disrespect me?
You have a point, we
hate those kind of girls.
She started it...
I finished it.
Isn't the plan to stay
away from trouble?
I guess they didn't
get the memo.
At least you're okay.
I'm okay.
I didn't faint. I just fell asleep.
If the President didn't bring me here
it could've been a lot worse.
That made me hungry.
Do you guys have snacks?
I knew it.
He's so sweet.
It's a little cold.
Thanks.
Ms. Zein Shion...
What do you want?
Do you want to fight again?
Ms. Shion.
What's happening?
Ms. Zein Shion.
I humbly ask for your forgiveness.
I lost my mind for a bit.
I didn't know what I was doing.
Please forgive me.
Oh my God.
Public apology speed run?
Please forgive me.
Ms. Shion...
Please.
Ms. Shion, please!
Forgive me!
I'm not ready to die!
Fine.
Whatever.
Stand up and leave.
I want to eat in peace.
Thank you...
Thank you, Ms. Shion.
Thank you.
Let's go! Let's go!
And why is the SSG Vice President
begging for your forgiveness?
Let's not think about it.
I'm too hungry for that.
Yum.
Hi, good evening, how are
you? Take a mask please.
This place finally feels
like a normal school.
I think that's their intention
to distract us from what's happening.
So it's easier to control us.
But it's not so bad to
have a little fun, right?
You're right.
Yeah, but don't forget
we still have to take precautions.
Let’s stay here.
I didn't it'll be a full house tonight.
Girls...
stay close.
Stay by our sides, okay?
Even if it's Free Bloody Night
we still can't trust them.
Aw, our heroes.
I'm still unsure why
Supremo isn't coming...
What's with the commotion?
What's up everyone!
It's red hair!
Is that Raze?
Okay...
that ruined the mood.
So this is what their usual
parties look like?
What more if it's a prom.
I hope we get to leave
before we see that.
I don't even want to know
their gimmick for that.
My mask is so itchy!
But you know guys...
I like costume parties.
What if they choose
your costume?
Pass!
Good evening, ladies
and gentlemen.
My name is Fritzy.
Your host for the night.
A round of applause please!
So many wonderful outfits
and looks tonight...
I'm so happy!
It's giving mystery glam!
Oh...
I see.
Even with these stylish
outfits provided
the newbies still look ugly.
That’s okay,
you're wearing masks.
No need to be ashamed.
Anyway.
Let's get this party started
by welcoming the guests of honor.
The administration
of Hell University.
First up
the head of the Supreme
Student Government
SSG advisor.
Ms. Katherine Velasquez.
Next stop!
The Vice President
of Hell University.
You know him as the creator
of The Bloody Night
also known as Freedom Night.
Please give a warm welcome
Mr. Francisco Agustin.
It can't be.
What the...
the old man is part of the admin?
That bastard!
Thought he was just a caretaker.
They played us like a fiddle.
Crazy.
Now...
Let me ask you.
Are you ready Hell U?
I said, are you ready!?
Last but definitely not the least,
your favorite and mine,
Madam Violet Rivera!
Thank you for that very
spirited introduction, Fritzy.
I'm overjoyed to see each
and every one of you.
But I won't make this speech long
cause I know you're
all ready to party.
Students...
estemeed guests.
By the power vested in me
as the headmistress of Hell University
I declare that now is the official start
of this year's
acquaintance party.
Please enjoy the night.
Cheers!
Good evening, Ms. Shion.
Vice President,
what pleasure do I owe you?
I haven't congratulated
you formally.
For being the new.
Supreme Student
Government Secretary.
Am I supposed to
be happy about that?
Just give it to the one
that's thirsty for that position.
It's the Supremo's decision,
his orders are absolute.
You have no choice.
I have no choice either.
Be happy, Ms. Shion.
Supremo's really particular
in choosing his secretary.
Because of that position
you quickly climbed to the ninth rank.
What?
I'll take my leave then.
Congrats again, Ms. Shion.
Oh my god!
That's so fast!
Rank nine!?
And the secretary too?
Whatever curse you have,
can I have some of it?
Your luck is overflowing!
You can leave this place, Zein!
And rank nine...
of all the ranks you've received
that's the highest you've achieved.
Congrats, Zein!
That's our girl!
Cheers!
Zein!
Zein...
don't accept that position.
Don't forget, this
is still Hell University.
Everything here has
consequences.
Calm down, Matt.
Let Zein decide for herself.
It's her choice, remember?
Dave's right, Matt.
Let Zein make her own decision.
Let her leave this hell.
And she can get help
from the outside.
Are you going to accept
the position, Zein?
That girl!
I'll think about it.
Excuse me.
Zein!
Is it the promotion?
Bad idea if you ask me.
You have to hold a knife
if you accept that position.
You should've been dead by now
if he wasn't keen on protecting you.
But he can't protect you forever.
Hold the knife, Zein. Before it's too late.
Who are you?
- Answer me!
- Miss, take it easy!
Sorry...
Did you find Zein?
It's too dark outside
and everyone's wearing masks.
I almost got lost.
Matt, this is your fault!
You should've have pressured her.
Aren't you curious why she got
that position so easily?
What?
It's a little too convenient
- don't you think?
- What do you mean?
Why does it seem like you
don't want us to be happy for Zein?
That's not my intentions,
I'm just worried for her!
- Oh my God!
- Dave!
Shit!
- Bro, are you okay?
- Dave!
Shit!
Since when did Dave's tolerance
for alcohol get so low?
Dave...
Shit, let's bring him to the clinic!
Dave, are ou okay?!
Zein...
Zein!
Matt, help me! He's in a bad shape.
Shit!
Where did Matt go?
Where is he?
Zein!
They drank the same thing.
Fuck!
Dave, wake up!
Dave!
Zein?
Zein...
What happened?
Zein?
Help, please!
Their drink was compromised
by an illegal drug.
They drank a high dosage,
that's why they're like this.
Zein...
Can't you see she's
literally dying already!?
Let's wait for the doctor.
Excuse me.
Whoever did this,
I swear I won't forgive him.
She needs to be treated right away
but nobody seems to care
in this goddamn place!
Aren't you happy that there
will be no bloodshed tonight?
What about what happned earlier,
what do you call that?